Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958 RL.00655
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Lorillard (Old Gold Cigarettes), 1940-1944; 30
  - Other Programming, 1940-1944; 67
    - Campus News, commercials, 1942 Oct. (Film-reel 210)
    - Chicago WENR, 1941 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 188)
    - Columbus, Oh. WHKC, 1940 Dec.-1941 Mar. (Film-reel 188)
    - Detroit WJR--Good Morning in Music, 1941 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 188)
    - Detroit WJR--Old Gold Sports Review with Tommy Harmon, 1941 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 188)
    - Four Corners USA, 1941 Feb.-Aug. (Film-reel 187)
    - Fulton Lewis, 1942-1944 (Film-reel 211)
    - Gloom Dodgers, 1942 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 210)
    - Good Morning in Music--Commercials, WJR, 1941 Oct.-1942 Jan. (Film-reel 244)
    - KOA, 1942 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 189)
    - Miami WKAT, 1941 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 188)
    - Nelson Eddy, 1942 Apr.-Nov. (Film-reel 209)
    - Nelson Eddy, 1942 Dec.-1943 Jan. (Film-reel 210)
    - New program announcement--Four Corners USA, 1941 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 188)
    - Old Gold Sports Review with Tommy Harmon, 1942 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 189)
    - Philadelphia WFIL, 1940 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 188)
    - Racing News, Clem McCarthy, 1944 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 212)
    - Richard Rollmand and Gracie Benrie--Spot announcements, 1940 Dec.-1941 Nov. (Film-reel 188)
    - Sports News with Bill Stern, 1942 Oct.-1943 Jan.; 1943 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 210)
    - Sports Round Up, 1943 Sept.-1944 Nov. (Film-reel 212)
      Week of May 8 missing
    - Sports Roundup WISH, 1942 Oct.-1943 Jan. (Film-reel 189)
    - Spot announcements, 1941 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 188)
    - Spot announcements, 1942 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 210)
    - Spot announcements, 1942-1944 (Film-reel 211)
    - Tommy Harmon Sports Review--Commercials, WJR, 1941 Oct.-1942 Mar. (Film-reel 244)
    - Tommy Riggs, 1941 Apr.-Oct. (Film-reel 187)
    - Vadeboncoeur, WSYR news, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 211)
    - Vadeboncoeur, WSYR news, 1944 Aug.-Nov. (Film-reel 212)
    - Washington WINX, 1941 Oct. 16 (Film-reel 188)
    - WHN, WGN, WOL, WWDC--Baseball play by play, 1943 Aug.-Oct. (Film-reel 192)
    - WTAG--Commercials, 1940 Dec.-1941 June (Film-reel 188)
    - Yankee Network and WHN--Spot announcements, B1-B12, 1942 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 188)
  - Red Barber, 1942-1943; 68
    - Gloom Dodgers, 1942 Nov.-1943 Jan. (Film-reel 212)
    - Herbert Marshall, commercials, 1942 Apr. (Film-reel 192)
    - Old Gold Campus News, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 192)
    - Old Gold Gloom Dodgers, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 192)
    - Old Gold program, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 192)
    - Old Gold Record of the Day, commercials, 1943 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 192)
    - Old Gold Sports News with Bill Stern, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 192)
    - Old Gold Sports Roundup, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 192)
    - Old Gold/Fulton Lewis, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 192)
    - Old Gold/Vadeboncoeur, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 192)
  - Sammy Kaye, 1943-1944; 69
    - Record of the Day, 1943 Jan.-May (Film-reel 211)
      Last week of April missing
    - 1943 (Film-reel 210)
    - 1944 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 215)
      Two pages missing from Mar. 8 broadcast
    - 1944 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 243)
  - WGN, 1941-1943; 70
    - An Hour with Elson and Anson, 1941 Oct. (Film-reel 190)
    - Baseball play by play, 1942 Sept. (Film-reel 191)
    - Baseball play by play, 1943 Apr.-Aug. (Film-reel 191)
    - Bob Elson--Baseball play by play, 1941 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 189)
    - Bob Elson--Old Gold Show, 1941 Oct.-1942 Apr. (Film-reel 190)
      Van Bibber cigars, Friends pipe tobacco mentioned in Aug. 1 script.
    - Bob Elson--Baseball play by play, 1941 Aug.-Sept. (Film-reel 190)
      Muriel cigars mentioned in scripts
  - WHN, 1941-1943; 71
    - Brooklyn baseball play by play, 1942 Mar.-Aug. (Film-reel 188)
    - Brooklyn baseball play by play, 1942 Aug.-Sept. (Film-reel 189)
    - N.Y. Giants football play by play, 1942 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 189)
    - WHN Newsreel, 1942-1944 (Film-reel 211)
- Mentholatum, 1942-1947; 31
  - 15 minute news and spots, 1944-1945; 72
    - KMBC, 1944 July-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - KOA, 1944 July-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - KSL, 1944 July-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - KTAR, 1944 Nov.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - KTUL, 1944 July-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - KYW, 1944 Feb.-1945 Apr. (Film-reel 246)
    - Pacific Blue Network, 1944 July-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - Pacific Blue Network, What's Doing Ladies?, 1944 June-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WCFL, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WCKY, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - WCTN, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WGAR, 1944 Aug.-Oct. (Film-reel 246)
    - WGAR, 1944 Oct.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WGN, 1944 Aug.-Nov. (Film-reel 247)
    - WGR, 1944 Jan.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - WHBQ, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WJAS, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - WMAQ, 1943 Aug.-1944 Mar. (Film-reel 247)
    - WOR, 1943 June-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
      Apr. 7-July 30 missing
    - WQAM, 1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WSMB, 1944 July-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
  - 5 minute news and spots, 1943-1944; 73
    - KDKA, 1943 July-1944 Mar. (Film-reel 245)
    - KFBI, 1944 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 245)
    - KMOX, 1944 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 245)
    - KRNT, 1943 Nov.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 245)
    - Texas State Network, 1943 July-1944 Mar. (Film-reel 246)
    - WBT, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - WCAU, 1943 July-1944 Sept. (Film-reel 245)
    - WCAU, 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 246)
    - WCSC, 1943 July-1944 Mar. (Film-reel 246)
    - WDSU, 1944 July-Sept. (Film-reel 246)
    - WFBM, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 245)
    - WISN, 1944 Aug.-Sept. (Film-reel 245)
    - WJR, 1943 July-1944 Mar. (Film-reel 245)
    - WMOB, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - WOOD, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 245)
    - WSB, 1943 July-1944 Mar. (Film-reel 246)
    - WSB, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - WSIX, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - WTAM, 1943 July-1944 Mar. (Film-reel 245)
    - WTAR, 1944 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 246)
    - WTMA, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 246)
    - WWJ, 1944 July-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 245)
  - Commercials, 1942-1947; 74
    - Commercials, Station breaks, 1942; 1945 (Film-reel 259)
    - Commercials, Station breaks, 1945 (Film-reel 260)
    - Commercials, Station breaks, 1945 (Film-reel 261)
    - WHO, 1943 July-1944 May (Film-reel 259)
    - WSGN, 1944 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 259)
    - 1947 Nov. (Film-reel 360)
  - Mentholatum Mountaineers, 1944-1946; 75
    - Auditions, spots, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 717)
    - 1944 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 237)
    - 1945 Mar.-1946 Jan. (Film-reel 278)
    - 1946 Jan. (Film-reel 307)
    - 1946 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 308)
  - Other Programming, 1943-1944; 76
    - Chain Breaks, 1943 July-Sept. (Film-reel 245)
    - Closing, 1943 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 245)
    - Iowa Barn Dance Frolic, WHO, 1943 Aug.-Nov. (Film-reel 259)
    - Texas Quality Network--Early Birds, 1944 July-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WAPI Hayloft Jamboree, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WLW Victory Girl program, 1943 June-1944 May (Film-reel 247)
    - WRNL Mail Bag Program, 1944 Aug.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 247)
    - WSGN 10 minute news program, 1943 July-1944 Feb. (Film-reel 247)
  - Spot announcements, 1942-1946; 77
    - Barn Dance spot announcements, 1942 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 174)
    - Recorded spots, 1944 Nov. 13 (Film-reel 278)
    - Recorded spots, 1946 (Film-reel 307)
    - 1943 Sept.-1945 Mar. (Film-reel 245)
    - 1943 July-1945 Mar. (Film-reel 245)
    - 1944 July-1945 Feb. (Film-reel 247)
- Nestle, 1930-1937; 32
  - Commercials, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 12)
  - Nestle Chocolateers, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 11)
  - Nestle Chocolateers, 1931; 1933-1937 (Film-reel 12)
  - Nestle Chocolateers--Len Joy and Orchestra, 1932 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 244)
  - Nestle Chocolateers--Phil Spitalnyd and Orchestra, 1932 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 244)
- Northam Warren (Cutex, Odorono), 1933-1942; 33
  - Cutex commercials, 1939 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 174)
  - Cutex Program, 1935 June-Aug. (Film-reel 10)
  - Niela Goodelle, 1935 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 134)
  - Odorono spot announcements, 1942 Oct. (Film-reel 174)
  - Phil Harris Orchestra, 1933 June-1934 Dec. (Film-reel 134)
  - Spots, 1939 May (Film-reel 134)
- Owens Illinois Glass Co., 1943-1947; 34
  - Broadway Matinee, 1943-1944; 78
    - Fred Waring, 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 239)
    - 1944 Jan. (Film-reel 237)
    - 1944 Jan.-July (Film-reel 238)
      No broadcast on June 6 (D Day); see reel 259 for Apr. 7 and 14 broadcasts
    - 1944 July-Aug. (Film-reel 239)
    - 1943-1944 (Film-reel 259)
      No broadcast on June 6, 1944--D-Day
  - Other Programming, 1943-1947; 79
    - Commercials, 1947 July-Sept. (Film-reel 360)
    - Fred Waring, 1945 Jan.-May (Film-reel 278)
    - Fred Waring, 1945 Jan. 4 (Film-reel 308)
    - Homefront Matinee, 1943 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 205)
- P. Ballantine & Sons, 1936-1954; 35
  - Programming, 1936-1954; 80
    - Ballantine Ale quart bottle--Spot announcements 1-10 over WCAX, 1942 June (Film-reel 199)
    - Baseball commercials, 1947 Apr. (Film-reel 366)
    - Baseball rained out games, 1949 May 22; July 10 (Film-reel 720)
    - Believe It Or Not, 1950 Jan.-June (Film-reel 721)
      To Part II, page 14 of June 1
    - Believe It Or Not, 1950 June-Sept. (Film-reel 722)
      From Part II, page 15 of June 1
    - Boxing, 1949 Jan.-1950 Feb. (Film-reel 720)
    - Broadway Showtime, 1944 (Film-reel 234)
    - Broadway Showtime, 1943 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 234)
      No broadcast June 12, Nov. 6; Sept. 18 broadcast never received
    - Commercials, 1945 Apr. 12 (Film-reel 275)
    - Commercials, 1947 (Film-reel 365)
    - Dinty's 3-Ring Sports Dugout, 1947 Aug.-1948 Jan. (Film-reel 365)
    - Dinty's 3-Ring Sports Dugout commercials, 1948 Jan.-May (Film-reel 422)
    - Fights, 1948 June-Sept. (Film-reel 422)
    - Foreign Intrigue, 1952 (Film-reel 974)
    - His Honor the Barber (Barry Fitzgerald), 1946 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 305)
    - His Honor, The Barber, 1945 oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 275)
    - Home of Champions, 1952 (Film-reel 974)
    - Merchandising record, 1941 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 199)
    - Milena Miller, 1945 Apr. 18 (Film-reel 275)
    - N.Y. Yankees vs. Giants, 1949 June. 27 (Film-reel 717)
    - Radio, 1954 Mar.-Sept. (Film-reel 989)
      Includes pre-season
    - Scott & Grauer television show, 1947 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 365)
    - Scott & Grauer television show, 1948 (Film-reel 422)
    - Special dealer record, 1940 Sept. 18 (Film-reel 199)
    - Television, 1954 Mar.-June (Film-reel 989)
    - Television, 1954 June-Sept. (Film-reel 990)
    - Television--Boxing, 1948 July-Nov. (Film-reel 422)
    - The Ballantine Show, 1945 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 275)
    - Three Ring Round Up--Commercials, 1942 June-Oct. (Film-reel 199)
    - Three Ring Round Up--Scripts, 1942 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 199)
    - Tri-City Distributing Co., 1936 Apr.-May; 1938 Feb.-June (Film-reel 133)
    - TV Film commercials, 1949 Feb.-June (Film-reel 717)
    - With General Cigar--Exhibition games, 1948 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 717)
    - Yankee Football, 1947 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 366)
    - Yankee Football, 1948 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 422)
  - Spot announcements, 1940-1952; 81
    - 1947 Sept.1948 Apr. (Film-reel 422)
    - 1940 July-Nov. (Film-reel 199)
    - 1952 (Film-reel 974)
    - Ale, 1941 Apr.-July (Film-reel 199)
    - Ale and beer for Puerto Rico, 1941 June 4 (Film-reel 199)
    - Beer, 1941 May 7 (Film-reel 199)
    - Ted Steele, 1941 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 199)
  - Three Ring Time, 1940-1943; 82
    - Bob Crosby, Chas. Laughton, Milton Berle, etc., 1941 Sept.-1942 June (Film-reel 199)
    - Guy Lombardi and Ogden Nash, 1943 Mar.-Sept. (Film-reel 199)
    - Guy Lombardi and Ogden Nash, 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 200)
    - Guy Lombardi and Ogden Nash, spot announcements, 1943 Feb.-Sept. (Film-reel 200)
  - Yankees Baseball, 1947-1952; 83
    - Commercials, 1948 June-Oct. (Film-reel 422)
    - Radio, 1949-1950 (Film-reel 720)
    - Simulcast, 1951 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 788)
    - Simultaneous radio and television, 1949-1950 (Film-reel 721)
    - Television, 1949-1950 (Film-reel 720)
    - Television, 1951 July-Sept. (Film-reel 788)
    - 1947 Mar.-May (Film-reel 365)
    - 1947 May-Sept. (Film-reel 366)
    - 1948 Mar.-June (Film-reel 422)
    - 1948 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 422)
    - 1952 (Film-reel 974)
    - Radio, 1952 Mar.-Apr. 30 (Film-reel 908)
    - Radio, 1952 Apr. 30-Sept. 4 (Film-reel 909)
    - Radio, 1952 Sept. 4-28 (Film-reel 910)
    - Television, 1952 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 910)
- Penick & Ford, 1930-1949; 36
  - Brer Rabbit molasses, 1930-1946; 84
    - 1946 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 308)
    - Agnes White, KFI California Home, 1941-1943 (Film-reel 192)
    - Commercials, 1941 Feb.-Oct. (Film-reel 170)
    - Commercials, 1942 Aug.24 (Film-reel 171)
    - Ida Bailey Allen, 1930 Sept.-1931 Mar. (Film-reel 155)
    - Ida Bailey Allen, coastal stations, 1930 Sept.-1931 Mar. (Film-reel 155)
    - Marjorie Mills Participation program, 1941-1943 (Film-reel 192)
      Mr. Seaburgh's files
    - Martha Brooks, WGY Market Basket, 1938-1943 (Film-reel 192)
    - Spot announcements, 1935 (Film-reel 155)
    - Spot announcements, 1937 (Film-reel 155)
    - Spot announcements live, 1937 (Film-reel 155)
    - Spot announcements live and recorded, 1938 (Film-reel 155)
  - Vermont Maid syrup, 1931-1938; 85
    - Spots and recordings, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 155)
    - Vermont Lumberjacks, 1931-1932 Mar. (Film-reel 155)
      some scripts by Eleanor Norton
    - Vermont Lumberjacks, coastal stations, 1931 Jan.-1932 Mar. (Film-reel 155)
  - Other Programming, 1934-1949; 86
    - Brer Rabbit, 1949 (Film-reel 718)
    - Br'er Rabbit commercials, 1947 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 360)
    - Br'er Rabbit commercials, 1948 Jan.-May (Film-reel 418)
    - Br'er Rabbit gingerbread flour spot announcements, 1937 (Film-reel 155)
    - Br'er Rabbit syrup and molasses, 1945 (Film-reel 264)
    - Br'er Rabbit syrup commercials, 1942 July 31 (Film-reel 171)
    - Br'er Rabbit syrup spot announcements, 1934 Oct.4 (Film-reel 155)
    - Legal and client OK's, 1942 (Film-reel 171)
- Planters Peanuts, 1940-1947; 37
  - Commercials, 1940-1947; 87
    - American Institute of Food Products, 1942 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 171)
    - NBC, 1942 Jan.-July (Film-reel 243)
    - Vacuum can, 1941 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 173)
    - WEAF, 15 minute program, 1942 Mar.-Apr. (Film-reel 243)
    - Westinghouse stations Philadelphia, 15 minute program, 1942 Mar. (Film-reel 243)
    - WFLA, 5 minute, 1941 Dec.-1942 Mar. (Film-reel 243)
    - WIOD, 15 minute program, 1941 Dec.-1942 Mar. (Film-reel 243)
    - WIOD, 5 minute, 1941 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 243)
    - WJAX, 5 minute, 1941 Dec.-1942 Mar. (Film-reel 243)
    - WJSV 1 minute, 1942 Jan. (Film-reel 243)
    - WJSV, 15 minute program, 1942 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 243)
    - WRC, Bruckhage News, 1942 Mar. (Film-reel 243)
    - WTIC, 1947 Jan.-July (Film-reel 362)
    - WTIC, 1947 Aug.-Oct. (Film-reel 363)
    - WTIC 15 minute program, 1941 Oct.-1942 Mar. (Film-reel 243)
    - 1940 Oct.-1941 Jan. (Film-reel 171)
    - 1942 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 171)
    - 1942 July-Dec. (Film-reel 172)
    - 1940-1943 (Film-reel 173)
    - 1943 Jan.-May (Film-reel 209)
    - 1943 May-1944 Jan. (Film-reel 262)
    - 1944 Jan.-1945 Oct. (Film-reel 263)
    - 1945 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 264)
  - Other Programming, 1941-1946; 88
    - 15-Minute News, 1946 (Film-reel 308)
    - American Institute of Food Products, 1941 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 171)
    - Peanut Oil and Magic Mixer audition, 1941 May (Film-reel 171)
    - Planter's Cocktail Peanuts, 1941 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 171)
    - Script, 1941 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 171)
    - WEAF--Peanut butter, 1943 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 202)
    - WRC--Peanuts, 1943 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 202)
    - WTIC--Peanuts, 1943 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 202)
- Radio Corporation of America (RCA), 1944-1954; 38
  - Curtain Call, 1952; 89
    - Azaya, 1952 July 4 (Film-reel 913)
    - Carrie Marr, 1952 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 914)
    - Concert in Brooklyn, 1952 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 914)
    - Mutiny in the Zoo, 1952 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 914)
    - Season of Divorce, 1952 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 913)
    - Summer Evening, 1952 July 25 (Film-reel 913)
    - Swell Girl, 1952 Aug. 1 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Liar, 1952 Aug. 22 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Model Millionaire, 1952 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Model Millionaire, 1952 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 914)
    - The Party, 1952 July 18 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Promise, 1952 June 20 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Soul of the Great Bell, 1952 June 27 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Summer People, 1952 Aug. 29 (Film-reel 913)
    - Vexations of A.J. Wentworth, 1952 Aug. 15 (Film-reel 913)
  - Dennis Day, 1952-1954; 90
    - 1952 Feb.-June, Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 914)
    - 1953 Jan.-June, Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 977)
    - 1954 Jan.-June (Film-reel 977)
  - Music America Loves Best, 1947-1949; 91
    - 1947 (Film-reel 362)
      Missing Oct. 19
    - 1948 Jan.-June (Film-reel 419)
    - 1948 June-Dec. (Film-reel 420)
    - 1949 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 717)
  - Phil Harris/Alice Faye Show, 1951-1954; 92
    - 1951 Mar.-May, Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 795)
    - 1952 Jan.-May, Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 915)
    - 1953 Jan.-June (Film-reel 977)
    - 1953 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 977)
    - 1954 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 981)
  - Other Programming, 1944-1954; 93
    - Academy Award Show, 1953 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 977)
    - Commercials, 1944 June (Film-reel 215)
    - Commercials, 1944 Oct. 15 (Film-reel 278)
    - Commercials, 1945 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 281)
    - Ezio Pinza Show, 1951 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 795)
    - Ezio Pinza Show, 1952 Jan.-June (Film-reel 914)
    - Hile Damroth commercials, 1949 (Film-reel 717)
    - Lifeline (Blood Bank show), 1951 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 795)
    - Martha Raye All Star Revue, 1953 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 977)
    - Meredith Willson's Music Room, 1952 June-Sept. 21 (Film-reel 914)
    - Meredith Willson's Music Room, 1952 Sept. (Film-reel 915)
    - Musical Merry-Go-Round, 1951 May-June (Film-reel 795)
    - Raymond Paige, A Battle of Music, 1945 Dec. (Film-reel 278)
    - Rex Saunders, 1951 May-June (Film-reel 795)
    - Screen Directors Playhouse, 1950 Jan.-June (Film-reel 717)
      No script for Jan. 13
    - Screen Directors Playhouse, 1950 June 30 (Film-reel 718)
    - Show of Shows commercials, 1950 Mar.-May (Film-reel 736)
    - Spot announcements, 1948 Mar. 18 (Film-reel 419)
    - Television, 1948 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 419)
    - The Goldbergs, 1953 July-Sept. (Film-reel 977)
    - The Music America Loves Best, 1944 Mar.-Dec. (Film-reel 239)
      Missing Oct. 15 broadcast
    - Theater Guild On The Air--Hamlet (with U.S. Steel), 1951 (Film-reel 795)
    - Today, 1952 June-July (Film-reel 915)
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1945 Jan.-Nov. (Film-reel 278)
    - Tony Martin, 1953 July-Aug. (Film-reel 977)
    - Transcriptions, 1950 (Film-reel 717)
    - What's New, 1944 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 239)
    - What's New--Lou Bring etc., 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 200)
    - Your Show of Shows (Caesar/Coca), 1953 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 977)
    - Your Show of Shows (Caesar/Coca), 1954 Jan.-May (Film-reel 977)
- Scott Paper Co., 1934-1955; 39
  - Programming, 1934-1955; 94
    - Bob Crosby Show, 1955 June-Dec. (Film-reel 992)
    - Commercials, 1934-1939 Mar. (Film-reel 137)
    - Commercials, 1939 Apr.-Dec. (Film-reel 139)
    - Omnibus, 1952 Dec. (Film-reel 915)
    - Omnibus, 1955 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 992)
    - Valiant Lady, 1955 Dec. (Film-reel 992)
  - Scott Towels, 1940-1941; 95
    - Charmingly We Live KEX, 1941 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 192)
    - Commercials, 1941 Sept. (Film-reel 179)
    - Commercials, 1940 Mar.-May; 1941 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 180)
    - Commercials, KFSD (Mr. Seaburgh's file), 1941 Oct. (Film-reel 200)
    - Commercials, KMOX (Mr. Seaburgh's file), 1941 Dec. (Film-reel 200)
    - Commercials, KPRC (Mr. Seaburgh's file), 1941? Dec. (Film-reel 200)
      And Yankees Network--WBAL, WBAP, KGKO, WBT, WCAD, WFLA, WGAR, WGY, WJAX, WJR, WJZ, WLS, WLW, WSYR, WWL, WIDD
    - Dollars and Sense, 1941 Dec. (Film-reel 192)
    - Home Forum KDKA, 1941 Sept.-Nov. (Film-reel 192)
    - Homekeeper's Calendar, KOMO (Mr. Seaburgh's file), 1941 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 200)
    - Listen Ladies, undated (Film-reel 192)
    - Round Robin Review, 1941 Sept.-Nov. (Film-reel 192)
    - Special announcements CNL, 1941 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 192)
- Scripts, 1944; 40
  - Double Destiny, 1944 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 215)
  - Four Corners USA, 1944 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 215)
  - King's Row, 1944 July 6-11 (Film-reel 215)
  - The Frank Sinatra program, 1944 July 6 (Film-reel 215)
- Sealtest, National Dairy Association, 1937-1943; 41
  - Commercials, 1942 May.-1943 Dec. (Film-reel 343)
  - James Melton, 1937 Jan.-Oct. (Film-reel 34)
  - Legal OK's, 1938 (Film-reel 33)
  - Legal OK's, 1938 May-Oct. (Film-reel 34)
  - Rudy Vallee, 1942-1943 (Film-reel 343)
    California Office; Includes photograph of Vallee's dummy Sally Ann
  - Sealtest Village Store Program, Jack Haley, Dennis Day, 1943 July-Nov. (Film-reel 343)
- Seeck & Kade (Pertussin), 1930-1940; 42
  - Commercials, 1939 Nov. (Film-reel 153)
  - Frank Stretz and Orchestra--Spot announcements, KMBC, 1932 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 243)
  - Frank Strutz & Orchestra, 1931 Dec.-1932 Jan. (Film-reel 159)
  - Pertussin Play Boys, 1930 Dec.-1931 Apr. (Film-reel 159)
  - Spot announcements, 1938; 1940 (Film-reel 159)
  - Spot announcements, 1940 July 11 (Film-reel 173)
- Seven-Up, 1945-1946; 43
  - Dealer spots, 1945 Aug.-Nov. (Film-reel 278)
  - Dealer spots, 1946 Feb.-Apr. (Film-reel 308)
  - Fresh Up Show, 1945 Apr.-Dec. (Film-reel 278)
  - Fresh Up Show, 1946 Jan.-June (Film-reel 308)
  - Promotion spots, 1945 Aug. 15 (Film-reel 278)
  - Seven-Up Show--Barney Grant audition, 1945 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 361)
- Shell Oil, 1932-1943; 44
  - Commercials, 1935-1946; 96
    - 1935 June-1936 Dec. (Film-reel 113)
    - 1937 Jan.-June (Film-reel 115)
    - 1942 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 171)
      30-second spots
    - 1940 Apr.-May, Aug.-Sept. (Film-reel 180)
    - 1945 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 262)
    - 1946 Apr. 19 (Film-reel 305)
  - Other Programming, 1932-1943; 97
    - Audition, 1940 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 180)
    - Buffalo cut-in commercials, 1936 Mar.-1937 June (Film-reel 110)
    - Football and Sports Review Eddie Dooley, 1932 Aug.-Dec.; 1933 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 110)
    - Football and Sports Review Eddie Dooley, 1933 Oct.-Dec.; 1934 Sept.-1935 Mar. (Film-reel 111)
    - Joe Cook, 1937 Jan.-June (Film-reel 115)
    - Miscellaneous--Commercials, 1941 (Film-reel 181)
    - One minute spot announcements, 1941 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 181)
    - Scripts, 1940 (Film-reel 180)
    - Shell Bugle spots--Commercials, 1940 Sept.; 1941 Apr. (Film-reel 181)
    - Shell Comes to the Party, 1941 Aug. (Film-reel 181)
    - Shell Football Show--Commercials, 1941 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 181)
    - Shell gasoline and motor oil--Commercials, 1941 Apr. (Film-reel 181)
    - Shell Ground Crew Service--Spot announcements, 1942 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 202)
    - Shell Oil jingles, 1941 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 181)
    - Shell Oil Reporter, 1932 July-Sept. (Film-reel 100)
    - Shell Oil Reporter, 1932 July-Sept.; 1933 June-Aug. (Film-reel 101)
    - Shell Pigskin Parade--Commercials, 1941 Sept.-Nov. (Film-reel 181)
    - Shell Premium--Spot announcements, 1941 July (Film-reel 181)
    - Shell Show, 1934 Jan.-1935 Mar. (Film-reel 341)
      California Office; missing Jan. 22, 29, Feb. 5, 12 1934
    - Shell Show, 1935 Mar.-Apr. (Film-reel 342)
    - Shell Thermo-Fast Service--Commercials, 1941 Sept. (Film-reel 181)
    - Shell Winterizing--Commercials, 1941 Oct. (Film-reel 181)